我仍記得她眼角留下的那滴淚水
I still can remember the tear in her eye
當他對我施咒
並說了唯一一句「再見」
when she cast her spell and
said nothing more than "goodbye"
記憶老去，臉也已記不清
The faces fade as the memories age
童年跟人生
就這樣揮之而去
A lifetime lost
and a childhood thrown away
希望你在外面的世界
能過得平安無事
Best of luck to the world out there
and I hope you'll be okay
而我，
也已經能接受，
我在這邊的生活
Meanwhile,
I'm feeling right at home
with what I got around me
要是，
能沒人來煩我，
我就能自己一人
Seems like
I would be all alone
if no one ever found me
我已經不想看到你，
別來找我
If you come looking around for me,
leave me be
因為我現在只需要
我的摯友
'cause the only friends I've got
are all I need
獵人為了晚餐出門狩獵
The hunter finds his food for the night
他技藝精湛，
希望著今天的飯有著落
with a quick-sharp aim
and a hunger from deep inside
小熊總是跟著熊媽媽
The little bear goes where his mama will go
熊媽媽也總
確保小熊知道去哪
The mother bear goes
where the little cub knows to follow
每個人在這世界
都有自己的人生
The rest of them in the world out there
have a different way of life
而我，
也已經能接受，
我在這邊的生活
Meanwhile,
I'm feeling right at home
with what I got around me
要是，
能沒人來煩我，
我就能自己一人
Seems like
I would be all alone
if no one ever found me
我已經不想看到你，
別來找我
If you come looking around for me,
leave me be
因為我現在只需要
我的摯友
'cause the only friends I've got
are all I need
而我，
也已經能接受，
我在這邊的生活
Meanwhile,
I'm feeling right at home
with what I got around me
要是，
能沒人來煩我，
我就能自己一人
Seems like
I would be all alone
if no one ever found me
我已經不想看到你，
別來找我
If you come looking around for me,
leave me be
因為我現在只需要
我的摯友
'cause the only friends I've got
are all I need
我的摯友
They're all I need